Some people get into trouble no matter what they wear.
Striptease is a comedy, crime, drama film directed by Andrew Bergman.
Bounced from her job, Erin Grant needs money if she's to have
any chance of winning back custody of her child.
But, eventually, she must confront the naked truth: to take on
the system, she'll have to take it all off.
Erin strips to conquer, but she faces unintended circumstances when a hound dog of a Congressman zeroes
in on her and sharpens the shady tools at his fingertips, including blackmail and murder.
Erin Grant, played by Demi Moore.
David Dilbeck, played by Burt Reynolds.
Lt. Al Garcia, played by Armand Assante.
Shad, played by Ving Rhames.
Darrell Grant, played by Robert Patrick.
Malcolm Moldovsky, played by Paul Guilfoyle.
Striptease is a 1996 American black comedy film written, co-produced and directed by Andrew Bergman,
and starring Demi Moore, Armand Assante, Ving Rhames, Robert Patrick and Burt Reynolds.
Based on Carl Hiaasen's 1993 best-selling novel of the same name, the film centers on an FBI
secretary-turned-stripper who becomes involved in both a child-custody dispute and corrupt politics.
Moore was paid a then-unprecedented $12.5 million to star in Striptease,
making her the highest-paid film actress up to that time.
Released theatrically on June 28, 1996, by Columbia Pictures and produced by Castle Rock Entertainment with a $50
million budget, the film grossed $33 million domestically (47th place) and $113 million worldwide.
It was somewhat more successful in the subsequent video rental market.
However, it was panned by critics and won six Golden
Raspberry Awards including Worst Picture.
The film explores themes of dance, police, blackmail, striptease, satire.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.